webstudio.com 2009-11-06

# - About Back To The Beach Software

Back To The Beach's Privacy Policy

Back To The Beach Software, LLC (“The Beach” ) respects the privacy of our online visitors and recognizes the importance of providing a secure environment for them. We have adopted a Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information you provide us. This Privacy Policy details how The Beach safeguards the privacy of its online visitors. Please note that when you link to other sites from any of The Beach Web site links, The Beach Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities on, those other sites. Also, this Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes.

  * What personal information we may collect 
  * What other types of information we collect 
  * How your personal information may be used 
  * Who is collecting your information 
  * What choices you have regarding the collection, use, and distribution of your personal information 
  * Whether we collect information from children 
  * What cookies are and how we use them 
  * What are internet protocol addresses 
  * What to do if you want to correct or review your personal information 
  * How secure your personal information is 
  * What to do if you have a question or complaint

The Beach only collects personal information on a voluntary basis. If an online visitor submits information to The Beach, it will usually take the form of either: (1) the purchase of goods or services through our online stores, (2) product registration or registration for online contest participation, (3) message boards, (4) warranty registrations, (5) contest registrations, (6) a consumer complaint, and/or (7) surveys. Personal information collected may include your name, home address, phone number, e-mail address, age, gender, and/or birth date. We do not require this information to gain access to our sites, however, you will not be able to access certain areas that require registration or receive materials such as newsletters unless such information is provided. Visitors purchasing products or services through our online stores will be required to provide additional information such as a valid credit card number and expiration date.

Your Web browser or client software may transmit certain geographic information or information regarding the capabilities of your computer to The Beach. The Beach may use this information to generate aggregate statistics about our user community. This information is never linked to you, or your household, in any way.

The personal information you provide The Beach will allow us to fulfill your product or service order; alert you of new products, features, or enhancements; and/or notify you of upgrade opportunities, contests, or special events. We may also provide your personal information to our affiliates, or other companies or organizations which offer products which may be of interest to you. The Beach may enhance or merge the personal information collected at a The Beach site with data collected from third parties. Lastly, we may use your personal information for internal marketing, profiling, or demographic purposes, so we can adapt our products and services to better suit your needs. We do this to better understand and serve our customers.

When you are asked for information while on a The Beach site, you are sharing that information only with The Beach unless specifically stated otherwise. Some services, however, are provided in conjunction with partner companies. If another company other than The Beach is collecting your personal information, you will be notified at the time the information is collected. If you do not want your information shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of information by not using that particular service or by not providing any information at that time. 

Please be aware that advertisers or Web sites with links to our sites may collect personal information about you. Remember, The Beach Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, those other advertisers or Web sites.

As a general rule, The Beach will not disclose any of your personal information except when we have your permission. However, we may need to disclose your personal information to third party vendors to fulfill orders or to process mailings. In special circumstances, we may also disclose such information if there is a violation of our Terms of Service or Use Agreements or if we have a good faith belief that the law requires it. 

The Beach sites also have message board, where users can exchange ideas and communicate with one another. When posting to a message board, please be aware that the information is being made publicly available online.

The Beach allows you to control the way that we use personal identifying information that we might obtain. In fact, many of the "mailings" The Beach may send you, such as newsletters, have procedures within them to cancel the receipt of any future mailings. 

If at any time you wish to opt-out of: (1) providing us your personal information, (2) having your personal information shared with third parties, and/or (3) receiving information (via email or postal mail) about new products, services, or promotions, you can do so by E-mailing us at techsupport@webstudio.com.   
Please indicate in your request what publications or services you no longer wish to receive so that we may better address your needs.

Children Under 13  
Once a child states that their age is under 13, we do not collect or store any personally identifiable information such as name, address, or email address. 

Note to Parents:  
We recognize a special obligation to protect personal information obtained from young children. We urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses, or phone numbers, without permission, when online. No information should be submitted to The Beach by children 12 and under. Children under the age of 17 and over the age of 12 should encourage their parents to review this policy and to contact us if they would like to evoke our opt-out policy or to raise any concerns.

Cookies are a feature of your Web browser that allows Web sites to transfer bits of information to your computer for record-keeping purposes. A cookie stored on your computer can be used to "remember" things like your password, or that you have already registered. This allows us to speed up your future activities, saving the time you would normally spend entering information such as your password or registration. In addition, The Beach may use cookies to retrieve user information for promotional or marketing purposes.

An Internet protocol ("IP") address is the unique number assigned to your server or Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). The Beach may track such IP addresses for system administration, to report aggregate information, or to prevent our servers from being abused.

IF you would like to review or correct your personal information, click on [My Account](http://www.webstudio.com/site/shopper_lookup.asp). 

If for any reason you are concerned with the way we are using your personal information, or would like to request that we cease using such personal information, please e-mail us at techsupport@webstudio.com.

The Beach has taken steps to assure that all information collected will remain secure and in its original form, i.e. free from any alteration. As such, access to all personal information is strictly controlled. When credit card information is transmitted, for example, we use industry standard, SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to assure that third parties to whom we transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of personal information.

Your credit card number is encrypted (scrambled) with state-of-the-art technology so that no one else can read it. Your credit card transaction is cleared in seconds through our secure server. Thanks to encryption, we believe that on-line ordering is now safer than giving your card number to a telephone operator, or handing your card to a waiter in a restaurant. There is no safer way to make a purchase.

If you have any questions or wish to file a complaint, please feel free to e-mail us at techsupport@webstudio.com. 

By using The Beach Web sites listed herein, you signify your assent to the The Beach Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use these sites.

|  |   
---|---|---
